Nguyen Minh Kiet



• Birthday: 10/09/1998

Address: Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

BRIEF INTRODUCTION

Hi, I'm a Software Engineer who loves simplicity, neatness and uniqueness.

I started learning programming when I was 20 years old and it only took me six months to write my first application using my programming skills. Since then, I became a website programmer with nearly 3 years of experience, working as a front-end dev for 2 companies, along with a few personal projects.

Thanks to that, I have experience in front-end and back-end.

In recent years, I have been very focused on programming and website development. Now I am very confident that my abilities can meet the requirements of the business.

■ WORK EXPERIENCE

■ VAS Group - VAS Nghi Son, Viet Nam, 04/2023 - now

Established in 1998, VAS is now a system of billet and steel rolling mills with a total capacity of about 4.350.000 tons square billet and 2.500.000 tons of Rebar & Wire rod.

I hold the position of Software Engineer developing internal applications for the company and maintaining deployed software.

I built the UI and logic for the *Vehicle Manage* project (a website used to monitor the time vehicles enter and leave the factory in Thanh Hoa).

Maintain and develop Vehicle Weighing Software for all the company's factories.

At the Da Nang factory, I have successfully implemented the *eDelivery* project (a website used to register supplier delivery information).

In addition, I also develop a few other projects for the company internally.

We use technology: ReactJS, NodeJS, C# .NET, MSSQL Server, MongoDB,...

■ Cuong Khang Informatics, Việt Nam, 06/2021 - 03/2023

Cuong Khang Informatics is a software technology company in Vietnam. Established in 2008 and run by a team of software engineers and marketing experts who understand the market.

I hold the position of Software Engineer at the company. Programming and developing applications according to customer requirements.

Maintain and operate the Warranty Repair System deployed to partners such as: Phong Vu, Đien Thoai Vui, LaptopOne, Vietfirst, Hai Trieu clock, Alaska, ShopDunk,...

We use technology: C# .NET, MSSQL Server, ADO.NET, WebService, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery,...

■ SKILLS

Programming languages

JavaScript, TypeScript, C# .Net (I'm quite confident that I can catch up with other languages when needed very fast)

Front-end Technologies

- ReactJS: Hook, Redux, Formik, React Hook Form, Yup, React Query, Axios,...
- NextJS (TypeScript)
- HTML, CSS, Responsive, SASS (7-1 pattern)
- Semantic, SEO
- Boostrap, Material UI, TailwindCss, AG-Grid, Telerik UI

Back-end Technologies

- Protocols: REST, HTTP(S)
- Frameworks/Libraries: Node.js, Express.js, ASP.NET Core
- OOP, Web socket SignalR
- Database: MongoDB, MSSQL Server (Store Procedure, Function, Trigger,...)
 (I haven't used ASP.NET Core for a while)

Dev Tools

Git, Github, Gitlab, Postman, React Developer Tool, Redux Dev Tool, Figma, VS Code

Other skills

Teamwork, present, SEO.

■ PERSONAL PROJECTS

Portfolio

This is my personal website to introduce myself, designed and developed by myself.

Technology used: ReactJS, SASS (7-1 pattern), Responsive

Website: https://kietnm.com

Landing page & Ecommerce

These are websites about introducing products, brands,... And e-commerce. All of them are cloned by me from sample designs on the internet.

Technology used: HTML, CSS, JS, SASS (7-1 pattern), Responsive, Semantic

Website:

- Ecommerce GroceryMart: https://nmkiet.io.vn
- CeloBank: https://kietnm-landing-celobank.vercel.app
- Besnik: https://kietnm-landing-besnik.vercel.app
- Dental Care: https://kietnm-landing-dental-care.vercel.app
- Lesson: https://kietnm-landing-lesson.vercel.app

CRUD

These are websites that demo the basic functions of software applications such as: create, update, delete. And validation form with Formik.

Technology used: ReactJS, NextJS, NodeJS, Vercel Postgres, Formik, Yup

Website:

- CRUD với ReactJS: https://kietnm-reactjs.vercel.app
- CRUD với NextJS: https://kietnm-nextjs.vercel.app
- Formik với Yup: https://kietnm-formik-yup.vercel.app

■ EDUCATION

Software Engineering

HUIT - HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF INDUSTRY AND TRADE

• Shool year: 2016 - 2020

Major: Software Technology

· Level: Good

■ LANGUAGES

• English

Read and understand specialized documents.

Vietnamese

Native speaker.

■ CONTACT INFORMATION

• **Contract Contract Contract**

• Email: kietnm.contact@gmail.com

Website: https://kietnm.com

• CV English: https://kietnm.com/cv/resume-en.pdf

• CV Vietnamese: https://kietnm.com/cv/resume-vi.pdf

■ THANKS

Looking forward to hearing from you - Nguyen Minh Kiet